<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DepreStyle</string>
    <string name="tell_something_about_deprestyle">TELL SOMETHING ABOUT DEPRESTYLE</string>
    <string name="start_test">START TEST</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_deprestyle">Welcome to DepreStyle</string>
    <string name="learn_more">learn_more</string>
    <string name="join_us_now">join_us_now</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="fitness1">TODO</string>
    <string name="settings1">TODO</string>
    <string name="selfcare1">TODO</string>
    <string name="facts1">TODO</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="give_love_to_yourself">Give love to yourself</string>
    <string name="facts">Facts</string>
    <string name="self_care">Self Love</string>
    <string name="did_you_know">Did you know</string>
    <string name="fitness">Healthy Exercise</string>
    <string name="do_some_physical_activities">Improve your mood</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="mema_lang">How are you</string>
    <string name="score">Total score:</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="lifestyle">Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="retake">Retake</string>
    <string name="home">DepreStyle</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="backk">Back</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="add_new_task">Add New Task</string>
    <string name="example">Example</string>
    <string name="Journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="add_moment">What are you up to buddy?</string>
    <string name="time">time</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="how_are_you">How are you?</string>
    <string name="set_a_title_for_this_log_required">Entry Title</string>
    <string name="physical_activities">Physical Exercise</string>
    <string name="mental_activities">Mental Exercise</string>
    <string name="Bounce">1. Bounce!</string>
    <string name="PlayOutside">2. Go Play Outside</string>
    <string name="Walk">3. Get Your Walk On</string>
    <string name="Yogi">4. Become a Yogi</string>
    <string name="Run">5. Set Off That Runner\'s High</string>
    <string name="BuildMuscle">6. Build Your Muscles</string>
    <string name="try_some_of_these_exercises">Try some of these exercises</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="choose_something_and_lets_do_this">Choose something and lets do this!</string>
    <string name="bounceinfo">“You don’t need to jump, but bend your knees and bounce as quickly as you can for a few minutes,” “This is an easy way to oxygenate your brain and get some endorphins flowing.”</string>
    <string name="playinfo">“Just moving your body inside or out is exercise,”. “Choose whatever works for you, depending on your functioning level, energy, and preferences.”</string>
    <string name="walkinfo">“Practical wisdom suggests that doing something is better than doing nothing in terms of physical activity,” If depression has made you sedentary, start off slowly and gradually increase time and distance.”</string>
    <string name="yogiinfo">“Eastern traditions such as yoga have a wonderful antidepressant effect in that they improve flexibility; involve mindfulness, which breaks up repetitive negative thoughts; increase strength; make you aware of your breathing; improve balance; and contain a meditative component.”</string>
    <string name="runinfo">“The most tangible example of exercise stimulating certain brain chemicals is the runner’s high that many athletes report experiencing once crossing a certain threshold of exertion while running.”</string>
    <string name="buildinfo">“Strength training is about mastery and control,” “It requires full attention and concentration. More importantly, people can see the results, the outline of the muscles forming, from dedication and training.”</string>
    <string name="liftupmood">Lift up your mood by doing these activities!</string>
    <string name="factstitle">Enhance your knowledge about depression</string>
    <string name="didyouknow">Did you know?</string>
    <string name="what_is_depression">What is depression?</string>
    <string name="what_are_its_symptoms">What are its symptoms?</string>
    <string name="what_are_the_risk_factors">What are the Risk factors?</string>
    <string name="how_to_prevent_it">How to prevent it?</string>
    <string name="what_are_its_complications">What are its complications?</string>
    <string name="depreinfo1">Depression is a mood disorder that causes a persistent feeling of sadness and loss of interest. Also called major depressive disorder or clinical depression, it affects how you feel, think and behave and can lead to a variety of emotional and physical problems. You may have trouble doing normal day-to-day activities, and sometimes you may feel as if life isn\'t worth living.</string>
    <string name="depreinfo2">More than just a bout of the blues, depression isn\'t a weakness and you can\'t simply snap out of it. Depression may require long-term treatment. But don\'t get discouraged. Most people with depression feel better with medication and psychotherapy</string>
    <string name="depression">Depression</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="symptominfo1">Although depression may occur only once during your life, people typically have multiple episodes. During these episodes, symptoms occur most of the day, nearly every day and may include:</string>
    <string name="symptom2">• Feelings of sadness, tearfulness, emptiness or hopelessness</string>
    <string name="symptom3">• Angry outbursts, irritability or frustration, even over small matters</string>
    <string name="symptom4">• Loss of interest or pleasure in most or all normal activities, such as sex, hobbies or sports</string>
    <string name="symptom5">• Sleep disturbances, including insomnia or sleeping too much</string>
    <string name="symptom6">• Tiredness and lack of energy, so even small tasks take extra effort</string>
    <string name="symptom7">• Reduced appetite and weight loss or increased cravings for food and weight gain</string>
    <string name="symptom8">• Frequent or recurrent thoughts of death, suicidal thoughts, suicide attempts or suicide</string>
    <string name="symptom9">• Anxiety, agitation or restlessness</string>
    <string name="symptom10">• Unexplained physical problems, such as back pain or headaches</string>
    <string name="symptom11">• Slowed thinking, speaking or body movements</string>
    <string name="symptom12">• Feelings of worthlessness or guilt, fixating on past failures or self-blame</string>
    <string name="symptom13">• Trouble thinking, concentrating, making decisions and remembering things</string>
    <string name="symptom14">For many people with depression, symptoms usually are severe enough to cause noticeable problems in day-to-day activities, such as work, school, social activities or relationships with others. Some people may feel generally miserable or unhappy without really knowing why.</string>
    <string name="riskinfo1">Depression often begins in the teens, 20s or 30s, but it can happen at any age. More women than men are diagnosed with depression, but this may be due in part because women are more likely to seek treatment. Factors that seem to increase the risk of developing or triggering depression include:</string>
    <string name="risk_factors">Risk factors</string>
    <string name="riskinfo2">• Certain personality traits, such as low self-esteem and being too dependent, self-critical or pessimistic</string>
    <string name="riskinfo3">• Traumatic or stressful events, such as physical or sexual abuse, the death or loss of a loved one, a difficult relationship, or financial problems</string>
    <string name="riskinfo4">• Blood relatives with a history of depression, bipolar disorder, alcoholism or suicide</string>
    <string name="riskinfo5">• Being lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgender, or having variations in the development of genital organs that aren\'t clearly male or female (intersex) in an unsupportive situation</string>
    <string name="riskinfo6">• History of other mental health disorders, such as anxiety disorder, eating disorders or post-traumatic stress disorder</string>
    <string name="riskinfo7">• Abuse of alcohol or recreational drugs</string>
    <string name="riskinfo8">• Serious or chronic illness, including cancer, stroke, chronic pain or heart disease</string>
    <string name="riskinfo9">• Certain medications, such as some high blood pressure medications or sleeping pills (talk to your doctor before stopping any medication)</string>
    <string name="complications">Complications</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo1">Depression is a serious disorder that can take a terrible toll on you and your family. Depression often gets worse if it isn\'t treated, resulting in emotional, behavioral and health problems that affect every area of your life.</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo2">Examples of complications associated with depression include:</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo3">• Excess weight or obesity, which can lead to heart disease and diabetes</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo4">• Pain or physical illness</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo5">• Alcohol or drug misuse</string>
    <string name="complication6">• Anxiety, panic disorder or social phobia</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo6">• Social isolation</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo7">• Suicidal feelings, suicide attempts or suicide</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo8">• Self-mutilation, such as cutting</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo9">• Anxiety, panic disorder or social phobia</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo10">• Family conflicts, relationship difficulties, and work or school problems</string>
    <string name="complicationinfo11">• Premature death from medical conditions</string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="preventinfo1">There\'s no sure way to prevent depression. However, these strategies may help.</string>
    <string name="preventinfo2">• <b>Take steps to control stress,</b> to increase your resilience and boost your self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="preventinfo3">• <b>Reach out to family and friends,</b> especially in times of crisis, to help you weather rough spells.</string>
    <string name="preventinfo4">• <b>Get treatment at the earliest sign of a problem</b> to help prevent depression from worsening.</string>
    <string name="preventinfo5">• <b>Consider getting long-term maintenance treatment</b> to help prevent a relapse of symptoms.</string>
    <string name="what_can_i_do_to_help_myself">What can I do to help myself?</string>
    <string name="look_after_yourself">Look after yourself</string>
    <string name="practice_self_care">Practice self-care</string>
    <string name="keep_active">Keep active</string>
    <string name="challenge_your_low_mood">Challenge your low mood</string>
    <string name="connect_with_people">Connect with people</string>
    <string name="do_these">Give love by doing these:</string>
    <string name="lookafterinfo1">• <b>Get good sleep.</b> For lots of people who experience depression, sleeping too little or too much can be a daily problem. Getting good sleep can help to improve your mood and increase your energy levels</string>
    <string name="lookafterinfo2">• <b>Eat well.</b> Eating a balanced and nutritious diet can help you feel well, think clearly and increase your energy levels</string>
    <string name="lookafterinfo3">• <b>Keep active.</b> Many people find exercise a challenge but gentle activities like yoga, swimming or walking can be a big boost to your mood</string>
    <string name="lookafterinfo4">• <b>Look after your hygiene.</b> When you\'re experiencing depression, it\'s easy for hygiene to not feel like a priority. But small things, like taking a shower and getting fully dressed whether or not you\'re going out of the house, can make a big difference to how you feel</string>
    <string name="lookafterinfo5">• <b>Avoid drugs and alcohol.</b> While you might want to use drugs or alcohol to cope with any difficult feelings, in the long run they can make you feel a lot worse</string>
    <string name="practicescinfo1">• <b>Work out what makes you happy.</b> Try making a list of activities, people and places that make you happy or feel good. Then make a list of what you do every day. It probably won\'t be possible to include all the things that make you happy but try to find ways to bring those things into your daily routine</string>
    <string name="practicescinfo2">• <b>Treat yourself.</b> When you\'re feeling down, it can be hard to feel good about yourself. Try to do at least one positive thing for yourself every day. This could be taking the time for a long bath, spending time with a pet or reading your favourite book</string>
    <string name="practicescinfo3">• <b>Create a resilience toolkit.</b> This could be a list of activities you know improve your mood, or you could fill an actual box with things to do to cheer yourself up. Try including your favourite book or film, a notebook and pen to write down your thoughts or notes of encouragement to yourself. It might feel difficult or a bit silly to put it all together but it can be a really useful tool if you\'re feeling too low to come up with ideas later on</string>
    <string name="practicescinfo4">• <b>Be kind to yourself.</b> None of us achieve all our goals. Don\'t beat yourself up if you don\'t do something you planned to, or find yourself feeling worse again. Try to treat yourself as you would treat a friend, and be kind to yourself</string>
    <string name="keepactiveinfo1">• <b>Join a group.</b> This could be anything from a community project or a sports team to a hobby group. The important thing is to find an activity you enjoy, or perhaps something you\'ve always wanted to try, to help you feel motivated</string>
    <string name="keepactiveinfo2">• <b>Try new things.</b> Trying something new, like starting a new hobby, learning something new or even trying new food, can help boost your mood and break unhelpful patterns of thinking and behaviour</string>
    <string name="keepactiveinfo3">• <b>Try volunteering.</b> Volunteering (or just offering to help someone out) can make you feel better about yourself and less alone</string>
    <string name="keepactiveinfo4">• <b>Set realistic goals.</b> Try to set yourself achievable goals, like getting dressed every day or cooking yourself a meal. Acheiving your goals can help you feel good and boost your self-confidence, and help you move on to bigger ones</string>
    <string name="lowmoodinfo1">• <b>Keep a mood diary.</b> This can help you keep track of any changes in your mood, and you might find that you have more good days than you think. It can also help you notice if any activities, places or people make you feel better or worse</string>
    <string name="lowmoodinfo2">• <b>Challenge your thinking.</b> Students Against Depression have lots of information and activity sheets to try to help you challenge negative thinking</string>
    <string name="lowmoodinfo3">• <b>Try self-help.</b> If your depression is mild, you might find free cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) courses online which can help you tackle some of your negative thinking and avoid your depression growing worse</string>
    <string name="lowmood4">• <b>Contact a helpline.</b> If you\'re struggling with difficult feelings, and you can\'t talk to someone you know, there are many helplines you can contact. These are not professional counselling services but the people you speak to are trained to listen and could help you feel more able to cope with your low mood</string>
    <string name="connect_with_other_people">Connect with other people</string>
    <string name="connectinfo1">• <b>Keep in touch.</b> If you don\'t feel up to seeing people in person, or talking, send a text or email to keep in touch with friends and family</string>
    <string name="connectinfo2">• <b>Keep talking.</b> It might feel hard to start talking to your friends and family about what you\'re feeling, but many people find that just sharing their experiences can help them feel better</string>
    <string name="connectinfo3">• <b>Join a peer support group.</b> Going to a peer support group is a great way to share tips and meet other people who are going through similar things. See Useful contacts for support for anyone experiencing depression, while Students Against Depression offers student-specific support</string>
    <string name="connectinfo4">• <b>Use online support.</b> Online support can be a useful way to build a support network when you cannot, or don\'t feel able to, do things in person. Online forums like <a href="https://www.elefriends.org.uk/">Elefriends</a> and <a href="https://www.bigwhitewall.com/V2/LandingV2.aspx">Big White Wall</a> are specifically for anyone struggling with their mental health</string>
    <string name="two_weeks">In the last two weeks how do you feel...</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="btinfo1">DepreStyle uses Beck Depression Inventory (BDI) as its screening test. <a href="http://www.minddisorders.com/A-Br/Beck-Depression-Inventory.html">About BDI</a></string>
    <string name="btinfo2">Instructions:</string>
    <string name="btinfo3">1.) Proceeding to the test, you will be given a 21 self-administered questions that can be answered between 5 and 10 minutes</string>
    <string name="btinfo4">2.) Each question is designed to assess a specific symptom common among people with depression</string>
    <string name="btinfo5">3.) The test has no time limit, so take your time to read and understand every question in the test because you can no longer go back from the previous question</string>
    <string name="btinfo6">4.) Cancellation of test will make you lose the progress you\'ve made, so make sure to finish it until the end</string>
    <string name="btinfo7">5.) Upon completion, you need to tap the done button to save your result and go back to home page.</string>
    <string name="note">Note:</string>
    <string name="btinfo8">• Since this Beck Depression Inventory (BDI) is self-administered by the patient, the result of the test should be verified or better be diagnosed by a trained mental professional</string>
    <string name="btinfo9">• The lifestyle that will be given at the end of the test is just a <b>GUIDE</b> to possibly make the patient feel better and have a better lifestyle. It is not a <b>CURE</b>  for depression</string>
    <string name="i_am_ready">I AM READY</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="begintestinfo">Before confirming please make sure that you have read and understood the instructions stated. Please don\'t rush and just take your time for better result</string>
    <string name="popupstarttest">START TEST?</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="heading">Heading</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="note1">• After the test tap the <b>DONE</b> button to save your result and go back to Home page. You can see your previous test results by tapping the Icon at the top left corner of your screen at the Home page then tap History.</string>
    <string name="something1">something</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="really_cool_log_in_screen">REALLY COOL LOG IN SCREEN!!!</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="no_account_yet">No account yet?</string>
    <string name="sign_up"><b><u>Sign up now</u></b></string>
    <string name="extra">NAKAKA KILIG NA SIGN UP ACTIVITY</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login1"><b><u>Login</u></b></string>
    <string name="sign_up1">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="professionals">Professionals</string>
    <string name="websites">Websites</string>
    <string name="account_settings">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="resetPassInfo">Please enter your email for us to be able to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="create_your_account"><b>Create your account</b></string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last name</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="location_city">Location / City</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender:</string>
    <string name="password1">Password (must have at least 6 characters)</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="DepreStyle_Info">DepreStyle: A Mobile Based Depression Analyzer and Life Style Planner</string>
    <string name="total_number">/ 21</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="hotlines">Hotlines</string>
    <string name="check_this_out">Check this out!</string>
    <string name="check_this_out_info">We have some things that might be helpful to you, we provided some hotlines and websites for you buddy! go check them out by tapping the icon at the top left corner of your screen at the homepage then tap the one that you want see.</string>
    <string name="hotlines1">• <u>Hotlines</u></string>
    <string name="web1">1. Pacifica</string>
    <string name="weblink1"><a href="https://www.thinkpacifica.com/anxiety-peer-support-groups/">https://www.thinkpacifica.com/anxiety-peer-support-groups/</a></string>
    <string name="web2">2. TalkLife</string>
    <string name="weblink2"><a href="https://web.talklife.co/">https://web.talklife.co/</a></string>
    <string name="weblink3"><a href="http://www.mhpss.net/">http://www.mhpss.net/</a></string>
    <string name="weblink4"><a href="http://www.globalmentalhealth.org/">http://www.globalmentalhealth.org/</a></string>
    <string name="weblink5"><a href="https://18percent.org/">https://18percent.org/</a></string>
    <string name="weblink6"><a href="https://adaa.org/adaa-online-support-group">https://adaa.org/adaa-online-support-group</a></string>
    <string name="weblink7"><a href="https://www.elefriends.org.uk/">https://www.elefriends.org.uk/</a></string>
    <string name="weblink8"><a href="https://www.bigwhitewall.co.uk/">https://www.bigwhitewall.co.uk/</a></string>
    <string name="web8">8. Big White Wall</string>
    <string name="web7">7. Elefriends</string>
    <string name="web6">6. ADAA (Anxiety and Depression Association of America)</string>
    <string name="web5">5. 18percent</string>
    <string name="web4">4. MGMH (Movement for Global Mental Health)</string>
    <string name="web3"><![CDATA[3. MHPSS (Mental Health & Psychosocial Support Network)]]></string>
    <string name="other_mental_illnesses">What are other mental illnesses?</string>
    <string name="facts_source_info1">Sources: https://adaa.org/</string>
    <string name="facts_source_info2">https://www.mayoclinic.org/</string>
    <string name="self_love_source_info1">Source: https://www.mind.org.uk/</string>
    <string name="fitness_source_info1">Sources: https://www.everydayhealth.com/</string>
    <string name="fitness_source_info2">https://www.cbhscorporatehealth.com.au/</string>
    <string name="other_mental_illnesses1">Other Mental Illnesses</string>
    <string name="other_info1"><b>Anxiety</b> \nDepression and Anxiety Disorders: Not the Same Depression and anxiety disorders are different, but people with depression often experience symptoms similar to those of an anxiety disorder, such as nervousness, irritability, and problems sleeping and concentrating. But each disorder has its own causes and its own emotional and behavioral symptoms. \n \nMany people who develop depression have a history of an anxiety disorder earlier in life. There is no evidence one disorder causes the other, but there is clear evidence that many people suffer from both disorders.</string>
    <string name="other_info2"><b>Schitzo</b> \nSchizophrenia causes symptoms that are more severe than the symptoms of bipolar disorder. People with schizophrenia experience hallucinations and delusions. Hallucinations involve seeing or hearing things that aren’t there. Delusions are beliefs in things that aren’t true. People with schizophrenia may also experience disorganized thinking in which they are unable to care for themselves. he symptoms of schizophrenia are divided into two groups, generally referred to as “positive symptoms” and “negative symptoms.” This isn’t based on whether a symptom is good or bad, but on whether the symptoms involve what could be described as “adding” or “removing” a behavior. Positive symptoms involve adding a behavior, such as delusions or hallucinations. Negative symptoms involve removing behavior. For instance, the symptom of social withdrawal involves removing social interactions. \n \nSome of the early warning signs of schizophrenia may include: \n \nsocial isolation a loss of interest in activities moodiness a lack of any feelings making irrational statements surprising or unusual behavior an altered sleep schedule getting either too much or too little sleep an inability to express emotions inappropriate laughter violent outbursts acts of violence toward yourself, such as cutting yourself hypersensitivity to smells, touches, tastes, and sounds hallucinations, which often appear as threatening or condemning voices that may tell you to act in violent ways delusions</string>
    <string name="other_info3"><b>Bipolar</b> \nBipolar disorder causes strong shifts in energy, mood, and activity levels. A person with bipolar disorder will switch between extreme excitement, or mania, and depression. These shifts can affect your ability to perform daily activities. In some cases, a person with bipolar disorder may also experience hallucinations and delusions \n \nSymptoms of bipolar disorder People with bipolar disorder experience episodes of intense emotions. These include three main types of episodes: \n \nManic episodes are times of increased activity and energy. A manic episode can make you feel extremely happy or elated. Hypomanic episodes are similar to manic episodes, but they’re less intense. Depressive episodes are similar to those of people with major depression. A person having a depressive episode will feel severely depressed and lose interest in activities that they used to enjoy. To be diagnosed with bipolar disorder, you have to have at least one episode of depression that meets the criteria for a major depressive episode. You must also have at least one episode that meets the criteria for a manic or hypomanic episode.</string>
    <string name="other_info4"><b>Anorexia</b> \nConnection and Relationship between Anxiety and Eating Disorders Depression can lead to the development of eating disorders; likewise, eating disorders can also result in depression, as co-occurring disorders. For example, when being in a malnourished state, which is common in eating disorders, physiological consequences may result, such as poor mood states or feelings of worthlessness. Although depression and eating disorders are two separate illnesses, one state can certainly trigger the development of the other.</string>
    <string name="videos">Videos</string>
    <string name="play_video">Play Video</string>
    <string name="back_to_home">BACK TO HOME</string>
    <string name="create_report">Create Report</string>
    <string name="how_to_conquer_anxiety_my_anxiety_depression_story"><![CDATA[How to Conquer Anxiety | My Anxiety & Depression Story]]></string>
    <string name="source_testimonies1">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCOTjb5Gt9FD323fCnYrrmMg</string>
    <string name="source_testimonies2">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsT0YIqwnpJCM-mx7-gSA4Q</string>
    <string name="depression_suicide_and_the_power_of_hope_gill_hayes_tedxexeter">Depression, Suicide and the Power of Hope | Gill Hayes | TEDxExeter</string>
    <string name="how_i_overcame_depression_by_just_sitting_around_jonathan_schoenmaker_tedxdelft">How I overcame depression by just sitting around | Jonathan Schoenmaker | TEDxDelft</string>
    <string name="source_testimonies3">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsT0YIqwnpJCM-mx7-gSA4Q</string>
    <string name="cara_delevingne_s_powerful_life_advice_on_overcoming_depression_and_anxiety">Cara Delevingne\'s Powerful Life Advice on Overcoming Depression and Anxiety</string>
    <string name="source_testimonies5">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHbq_l1qnuomfJCYQTsWf_Q</string>
    <string name="conquering_depression_how_i_became_my_own_hero_hunter_kent_tedxyouth_cehs">Conquering depression: how I became my own hero | Hunter Kent | TEDxYouth@CEHS</string>
    <string name="source_testimonies4">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsT0YIqwnpJCM-mx7-gSA4Q</string>
    <string name="andrew_cripps_very_emotional_depression_anxiety_story"><![CDATA[Andrew Cripps - (Very Emotional) Depression & Anxiety Story]]></string>
    <string name="source_testimonies6">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCjAU49ue1WiPTEqVr5IFceQ</string>
    <string name="stories_about_depression">Stories about depression</string>
    <string name="watch_these_videos">Watch these videos:</string>
    <string name="hunter_kent">Hunter Kent</string>
    <string name="jonathan_schoenmaker">Jonathan Schoenmaker</string>
    <string name="gill_hayes">Gill Hayes</string>
    <string name="cara_delevingne">Cara Delevingne</string>
    <string name="andrew_cripps">Andrew Cripps</string>
    <string name="jess">Jess</string>
    <string name="video_exercise">Video Exercise</string>
    <string name="psychetruth">PsycheTruth</string>
    <string name="yoga_with_adriane">Yoga With Adriane</string>
    <string name="doctoroz">DoctorOz</string>
    <string name="popsugar_fitness">POPSUGAR Fitness</string>
    <string name="video_exercises">Healthy Video Exercises</string>
    <string name="feel_better_yoga_beginners_yoga_for_depression_stress_the_blues_anxiety_relief"><![CDATA[Feel Better Yoga – Beginners Yoga for Depression, Stress, the Blues & Anxiety Relief]]></string>
    <string name="source_exercise1">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGb34D3ThpmjLNn-FLv2_yQ</string>
    <string name="yoga_for_complete_beginners_20_minute_home_yoga_workout">Yoga For Complete Beginners - 20 Minute Home Yoga Workout!</string>
    <string name="source_exercise2">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFKE7WVJfvaHW5q283SxchA</string>
    <string name="equip_yourself_5_bodyweight_exercises">Equip Yourself: 5 Bodyweight Exercises</string>
    <string name="source_exercise3">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc8cHxAZ3jwWkrrDyaLwDUw</string>
    <string name="the_best_15_minute_beginner_workout_no_equipment_needed_class_fitsugar">The Best 15-Minute Beginner Workout — No Equipment Needed | Class FitSugar</string>
    <string name="source_exercise4">Source: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBINFWq52ShSgUFEoynfSwg</string>

    <!-- Spinner -->
    <string-array name="gender1">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
